Abhishek Potnis

Software Engineer at Microsoft

Summary

Currently I am working at Microsoft as a Software Engineer with Natural Language Experience (Microsoft Office). I have a Masters degree in Computer Science from University of Florida (GPA 3.67) and a Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering (GPA 3.67 again. Like to keep things constant;-)) from University of Mumbai. I have also interned at Microsoft in the summer of 2015. Being an avid coder I have actively participated in coding contests, Hackathons etc. and won a few of them. Interested in new and upcoming technologies.

Experience

Software Engineer at Microsoft

February 2016 - Present

Working with Natural Language Experience team as a part of Microsoft Office Engineering

Student at University of Florida

August 2014 - December 2015 (1 year 5 months)

Relevant coursework-

Machine Learning

Artificial Intelligence

Distributed Operating Systems

Analysis of Algorithms

Database Implementation

Advanced Data structures

Software Engineer Intern at Microsoft

May 2015 - August 2015 (4 months)

As an intern, I was working with Natural Language Experience team which is a part of Microsoft Office GSX team.

Education

University of Florida

Master's Degree, Computer Science, 2014 - 2015

University of Mumbai

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Engineering, 2010 - 2014

Activities and Societies: Literary council, College Student Council

Abhishek Potnis

Software Engineer at Microsoft



Contact Abhishek on LinkedIn